modamart.com 2012-10-05

# Clothing, Fashion Shoes & Womens Accessories--Modamart.com - Privacy Policy

**    1) ModaMart is committed to protecting your privacy.**

   This privacy statement discloses what information we gather about you when you visit the modamart.com site and describes how we use 

   that information. Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive from our site completely confidential and used solely for internal

   purposes. We will not share your personal information with any other parties.

**    2) Collection of your Personal Information:**

   The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail, phone. We may collect certain 

   information about your visit, such as type of browser you use; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the 

   site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site and 

   administer the site.

**    3) Use of your Personal Information:**

   The personal information collected on this site will be used to provide the services you have requested.

   We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including 

   critical updates and notifications. Additionally, we may send you information about other ModaMart products and services. All online 

   payment transaction is redirected at PayPal, we don't take your financial information. All our priority is to provide a safe and secure online 

   shopping experience for all of our customer.
